Wild at heart
Pandas is a documentary, family, adventure film directed by Drew Fellman.
In the mountains of Sichuan, China, a researcher forms a bond with Qian Qian,
a panda who is about to experience nature for the first time.
Narrator (voice), played by Kristen Bell.
Self, played by Wen Lei Bi.
Self, played by Rong Hou.
Self, played by Ben Kilham.
Self, played by Jacob Owens.
Self, played by Li Bingbing.
Kung Fu Panda is an American martial arts comedy media franchise that started in 2008 with the
release of the animated film Kung Fu Panda produced by DreamWorks Animation.
Following the adventures of the titular Po Ping (primarily voiced by Jack Black and Mick Wingert), a giant panda who is improbably chosen as the prophesied Dragon
Warrior and becomes a master of kung fu, the franchise is set in a fantasy wuxia genre version of ancient China populated by anthropomorphic animals.
Although everyone initially doubts him, including Po himself, he proves
himself worthy as he strives to fulfill his destiny.
The franchise consists mainly of four animated films: Kung Fu Panda (2008), Kung Fu Panda 2 (2011), Kung Fu Panda 3 (2016) and Kung Fu Panda 4 (2024), as well as
three television series: Kung Fu Panda: Legends of Awesomeness (2011–2016), The Paws of Destiny (2018–2019), and The Dragon Knight (2022–2023).
The first two films were distributed by Paramount Pictures, the third film was distributed by 20th Century Fox and the fourth was distributed
by Universal Pictures, while the television series respectively aired on Nickelodeon and Nicktoons, Amazon Prime, and Netflix.
Six short films: Secrets of the Furious Five (2008), Kung Fu Panda Holiday (2010), Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters (2011),
Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Scroll, Panda Paws (both 2016), and Dueling Dumplings (2024), have also been produced.
The franchise's first two features were nominated for the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature as well as numerous Annie
Awards, the first television series won 11 Emmy Awards and the third television series won two Emmy Awards.
All four films were critical and commercial successes, grossing over $2 billion overall, making it the seventh highest-grossing animated film franchise,
while the second film was the highest-grossing film worldwide directed solely by a woman (Jennifer Yuh Nelson) until Wonder Woman (2017).
The series is additionally popular in China as an outstanding
Western interpretation of the wuxia film genre.
The film explores themes of human animal relationship,
panda, wildlife, wildlife conservation, sichuan.